freshnewgames.com 2019-05-21

# Fresh New Games - Privacy Policy

This special page is here to explain you how freshnewgames.com is protecting your pivacy and how freshnewgames.com is not logging any information and not keeping track of any activities you perform on our website. Please read the following text carefully to understand what is happening with your information and why your privacy is safe at this website. 

**Your personal privacy**  
freshnewgames.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. freshnewgames.com does not collect any personal information. 

**Full Privacy**  
freshnewgames.com does not use or has any systems in place that store or process your behaviour. Your privacy is truely safe at our website. We are here to bring the best game experience to our users, it doesn't matter to use to know how many players are here or what our players are doing! We want you to have fun! 

**IP address and logging**  
Your IP address is not used to gather broad demographic information and we do not track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc). Our webserver log files are disabled and configured to take emergency dumps only in the event of a server crash. (EMERG log level) 

**Sharing Of Information**  
There are no scripts or programs running on our server that store your information. We allow our third party advertisers to host scripts on our webpages. Third party advertisers might collect, store and use your information. These scripts are not property of our game portal website and are subject to the privacy policy of the third party. Find the links to the third party privacy policies in the sections below to learn more. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit freshnewgames.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Please read the pages are cpmstar.com or google.com/adsense to learn more about the privacy policies of our third parties.

Google Privacy Policy : [google.com/privacy_cookies.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html)  
Google Cookie Policy : [google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

The scripts of our third parties are located on the servers of our third parties, freshnewgames has no control on the server(s) of our third parties. The privacy policy of any third party may change in the future. 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. You can opt-out for third parties cooking on [this external website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) runned by the NAI. 

**What are cookies?**  
Cookies are digital text files that can be created by any remote connection that you make in your browser. A cookie can only store text or (binairy) numbers or a combinations of both. Because cookies are just text files, created and controlled by your browser, it's a harmless system for your computer health. However you need to be aware that websites, mobile apps and advertisers are able to write and read certain 'invisible' information on the background while you think you are just browsing some online or mobile App content. Our website is NOT using performance cookies and is NOT tracking your behaviour. However we are using third-party advertisers that might use cookies - please read the third party section of our privacy policy for more information about our third parties. 

**Liability**  
It is freshnewgames.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, freshnewgames.com will immediately disable and remove games in question.
